Don't be scared.
I'm not into scaring.
Trust is the key to S&M play.
Trust me. I won't hurt you.
Someone like you...
What was your name again?
My name is Ai.
Someone as pure
and courageous as you, Ai,
is the only hope
for this rotten Japan.
I worship you.
You know how it is,
sluts who screw
around during college
and then end up marrying
doctors and bureaucrats.
I call those sluts "whores".
You're great.
Do you understand?
Great.
You are great.
No blindfolds, please.
Trust me.
Have trust in me.
Don't move!
The needle breaks
and then you die.
Tokyo Decadence
Hello?
Yes.
The New Prince Hotel.
7 p.m.
A Mr. Ishioka under
the name of Sato...
No, I'll kill time and go there.
Please.
Your fortune requires
you to followthree rules.
First, place a telephone
directory under your TV.
- The telephone book under the TV?
- Yes.
Second, don't go to
an art gallery in the east.
There's a thick
mist in that direction
and a woman alone
will be lost in it forever.
Yes.
And third,
find a pink stone,
make a ring out of it and
wear it on your middle finger.
You followthese three rules
and God says you will be happy.
Can you do that?
Yes, I can.
Thanks for waiting.
Please take a seat.
I looked through
what we recommended
and I recommend
this pink imperial Topaz.
I'm Ai.
Yes, I've just arrived.
He wants me
for three hours now.
I'm ready, sir.
Come over here.
- On your knees.
- Yes, master.
Cut the "master" crap.
We're not in some
stupid high school play.
Yes, I understand.
Good. A woman's
hair is a woman's life.
I understand why
the Nazis cut women's hair.
Stand on the window ledge.
Please drawthe curtain.
The point is, I get pleasure
out of humiliating you.
- Got that?
- Yes.
Wiggle your ass slowly as
you pull down your panties.
Slowly.
Five millimeters at a time.
Not like that.
Like a horny businesswoman.
You know, the ones
who are dying for a fuck.
Look around you.
They're everywhere.
Stupid horny businesswomen.
the ones who are
starved for stiff cocks.
You'll do it over
and over until you're wet.
What is that?
Don't laugh.
- Don't laugh.
- Ouch!
- Don't ever laugh.
- I won't.
You're just a
cunt living for a fuck.
You're a bitch in heat.
A bitch doesn't laugh
out of embarrassment.
Stupid bitch.
I got it, sir.
I promise I won't laugh.
- No, do it again.
- Yes.
No.
Yes.
Good.
No, no.
More.
Yes.
You're all wet.
Feeling good?
This what you wanted?
Say,
"I'm a horny businesswoman."
I'm a horny businesswoman.
Louder.
I'm a horny...
What? Now?
Wait, I'll ask her.
It's my woman.
She's a little weird herself.
She wants to come up here.
Do you mind?
A threesome? It'll cost you
ten-thousand more per hour.
Sure. So it's all right.
Come on over.
What were you doing just now?
Nothing.
Wasn't that sign language?
You do social work?
Only occasionally.
I go and visit little children.
But I study it because
I think it's beautiful.
- You want me like this?
- No, I want you naked.
- I'll go take a shower.
- Wait a minute.
Sit down.
- How old are you?
- I'm twenty-two.
Twenty-two...
So you've been alive
for twenty-two years?
Obviously.
Truth about yourself.
It's not as complicated as the
earth's axis or the structure of DNA.
It's more about yourself.
I've discovered that
I have no talent whatsoever.
I've lived for forty-four years.
I've done a lot of things.
All sorts of things.
Many things.
And there's only one thing.
I'm certain about.
Just one thing.
You know what that is?
It's the fact that
I'm a horny bastard.
Go take a shower.
Yeah, it's me.
You heard?
They're mad as hell over
the Yamato Enterprise deal.
Yeah, they got Yoshizaki.
Don't start whining now, you idiot.
Yeah, I called Yuko over.
Close the Singapore account.
They cut Yoshizaki's face.
Yeah, close the account.
Get every penny out.
Send your family
away somewhere.
Yeah.
See ya.
My woman.
She's downstairs.
Talk to her.
What's happening?
Tell her.
She's into it too.
A vibrator is...
Getting it with a vibe?
On your knees?
Yes.
And fastened by a rope?
Does he have a hard-on?
Well, he...
I bet he doesn't.
I bet he's coked up.
I can hear the vibrator.
I'm going up there.
You'll lick us there while we fuck.
You'll like us where we joined.
Press your ass against the mirror.
Shake your ass back and forth.
More.
You're a sex-starved bitch
who's so low no one
would even touch you.
So you do it with the
mirror while we watch you.
Isn't he vulgar?
You want it too, don't you?
Don't you?
It feels so good.
You want it, don't you?
Answer her.
Don't you?
You're going to lick us there.
I'm going.
'Til next time.
You paid me too much.
Never mind.
Wait.
Listen.
Don't think you've no talent.
That's a cop-out.
Take care.
Mr. Ishioka.
What'll I do?
You dropped something.
On your knees. Lick my feet.
- Stop it.
- Call me "Mistress."
Stop it, Yoko.
Mr. Satoh is not in.
May I take a message?
Has he checked out?
- No, he hasn't.
- Thank you.
Are you an S or an M, sir?
Both? An S and an M?
Fine.
And you're newto our club?
That "Fats Only" girl,
it's her birthday today.
Why such an expensive ring?
340 thousand?
All gone in one night.
You should have bought
one at a night market.
I thought a cheap
one wouldn't work.
I hate gloomy stories like this.
Ai, Miyuki, it's a threesome.
All right?
Which hotel?
The New Prince. 1-1-2-4.
Hello?
Yes?
They'll be there
in thirty minutes.
Your room number again?
1-1-2-4? Good.
Go on ahead.
Wait!
Leave her!
I'll go there with you later.
I can always call
the police on my cellular.
Thank you.
I've got a beard rash all over me.
Mistress! Mistress Ai!
I want to come again.
Give it a rest.
You can't get it up anyway.
I can too. Just one
more time. Pretty please.
You strangle me and up I go.
Strangle you?
Precisely... Prick-cisely.
Cunt-cisely.
Strangle me and jerk me off.
Ready, set, go!
I'm Kermit the Frog. Stop it.
Don't stop.
When I say stop,
squeeze harder.
Stop it.
No, he's quite young.
He's all doped up.
Yeah, crack.
Pupils?
The black part of his eyes?
The black part of his eyes...
They're dilated.
We run.
Don't forget anything.
My my.
I met my mother who died last year.
She said to me,
"Go away, you fool!"
Did I squirt my juice?
Here.
Thanks.
The ring is too big, isn't it?
Take it back and
have it made smaller.
This is Shida.
I'm in front of the new Tokyo
Metropolitan Government Office.
Pan the camera, please.
Isn't it gigantic?
Is it time?
Back to the studio then.
Are you ready, Miss Sanae?
Here's Miss Sanae's
"Super-cool Guys."
More and more of our artists
are working outside Japan.
Mr. Sudoh is one of them.
You're a voluntary exile?
Well, only half of the year.
So there are things you
can only do in London.
Yes, in the "hard" technology.
What's that?
I use a lot of acoustic instruments.
There aren't too many
studios left in Japan for that.
And they have better
mixing technicians there.
- So that's why, Mr. Sudoh...
- Stop this Mr. Sudoh business.
Talk to me like you usually do.
You'll be in Japan for a while?
During my son's entrance exams.
You're staying in your Beverly
Hills mansion in Yokohama.
You know it's no mansion.
My flat in London's more...
Miyuki comes in late today,
so there's only you.
Are you sick or something?
He's a good client.
I'm begging you, Ai.
If he likes you, he'll pay
you double, maybe triple.
He's not into hard stuff.
He likes talking to girls.
He's a nice guy.
I come here three times a week.
Go on, dig in.
You know, these restaurants with
movie star clientele are so pretentious.
Really?
How's the wine?
It's good.
Chateau Mouton, Rothschild '79.
I only drink this here.
That means I drink this
three times a week.
An obvious deduction.
Was that last year?
Suzanne Mildonian's harp...
it was something else!
Suzanne Mildonian's harp concerto.
It was in a small hall in
Vienna's Opera Theater.
It was wonderful. You can't
beat the real thing.
Would you like to
order anything else, sir?
No, no. We're fine.
All I want now is a beauty's smile.
Where's the manager today?
In Singapore, on business.
Oh, Mt. Fuji, thou
holiest of mountains.
My dream is to rape a dead woman.
It's called necrophilia.
It's the most beautiful
form of sex in the world.
I want you to play the
part of Umeko Yoshida.
who was raped near
Mt. Fuji on April 19, 1957.
She was murdered,
then raped by Toshio Yasaka,
an unemployed man
from Iwate Prefecture.
I'll strangle you lightly,
so pretend to die.
I'll examine you first,
then I'll rape you.
I'll pay you extra for the rape.
Are you ready to be raped, Umeko?
Right here in this forest,
under Mr. Fuji?
Umeko!
Sorry, but I'm leaving.
Give me back my money, then.
You saw him on TV?
First time in six months.
It's hard to date someone famous.
But you looked really happy then.
I want to go see him.
I shouldn't?
Don't do it.
But he never told me it's over
or that he doesn't like me.
He thinks he's being kind.
Sorry to bother you now,
but we got an M client.
You'll take him?
I'll go.
I'm fine.
Please don't leave
during the session again.
- Your name?
- Ai.
I'm Saki.
Aren't you glad
she's pretty, Turtle Face?
Call him Turtle Face, Ai.
Looks like a turtle, doesn't he?
I didn't know it was a threesome.
I'm sorry
but this one insisted
on having another Mistress.
We won't do
anything you don't like.
Go take a shower then.
There's a dress in there.
Put it on.
And the hat too.
How's your business going?
I heard the real estate
market is in a slump.
Yes, Mistress Saki.
But my company's motto
is "sound management,"
so we're doing all right.
Glad to hear that.
How beautiful.
It suits you.
Do you like the dress, Ai?
It's pretty.
Please sit down here.
Look, Turtle Face, you've
finally found a Mistress
who looks good in
an art deco dress.
Greet your Mistress.
Dear Mistress Ai.
Train me good and hard.
And what's your first request,
Turtle Face?
I'd like to kiss her feet.
Kiss her feet?
Yes.
What do you think of
his capricious wish, Ai?
Will you grant it?
You got your permission.
Just the sole's fine.
You're going too far, Turtle Face.
Come over here.
Sorry about this.
Have a drink and relax.
You're pathetic.
Give me your neck.
Come closer.
Good.
Who said you could
lick between my legs?
Say, "I'm sorry."
And look at me.
Forgive me!
Say, "I'm sorry."
Forgive me.
- I'm sorry.
- Forgive me.
Say, "I'm sorry," dammit.
Forgive me.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Mistress Saki.
I'm through playing with you.
Crawl backwards.
Stay still there.
Be still like a piece of stone.
Lift your bottom.
What are you doing?
You're bad. Come here.
Ai.
He's really a baldy!
How embarrassing.
You're all wet.
Feels good?
Go on, let's go.
Good, now pee.
It'll feel good.
Get the bed pan.
All right, Turtle Face.
Get the bed pan and crawl backwards.
Go back.
Further back.
Don't be a turtle. Get moving.
Don't spill a drop.
You're fine there.
Now, Turtle Face,
drink every drop of it.
I can't. I can only drink yours.
I only drink yours, Mistress Saki.
Mercy!
If you drink all of it, I'll reward you.
Now drink up.
All of it.
Every drop.
Here's your reward.
Raise your ass.
No, it hurts.
You like it, don't you?
You love it, Turtle Face.
You come. I'll kill you.
See you later.
Good evening, Miss.
Yes, what else?
And?
I see. All right.
I'll have the asparagus
and the smoked salmon.
And some pasta.
Yes, and make it quick.
- Is it good?
- Yes.
Hold the smoke between your legs.
It's sweet.
For a non-smoker,
you're good at it.
You must be wealthy.
Not really.
It's Japan that's wealthy.
But it's wealth without pride.
It creates anxiety, which
drives our men into masochism.
I've made my
living out of these men.
Well, here I go.
All I can do is sigh.
Your sweet kiss.
makes my virgin heart
dream sweet dreams of love.
Here, on this golden beach,
on this burning sand.
Let's love nakedly
like two mermaids.
We pressed our tanned cheeks together
and whispered our vow.
Let's keep it our secret forever.
Oh how it makes me sigh!
Ah, the joy of love.
The rose-colored days.
The first time I met you
was my love holiday!
So much!
Yes?
There's something I can't forget.
You want advice? Sure.
I want to go see him,
but he's married.
I feel scared.
Clarify your situation.
Learn to hate ambiguity.
That's my advice, always.
The answer is always one and the same.
Clarify your situation.
Blow up the earth,
whatever, but do that.
This blood...
is the same blood as the blood
that the first fish that
crawled onto land shed.
I want to evolve too.
I want to be able to live in a
totally different world.
Thanks for everything.
I'll go now.
Goodbye.
Wait.
This will give you courage.
It will make you superhuman.
For me?
Goodbye.
Take care.
It's a bit complicated.
Follow the road
beside the kindergarten.
You want a map?
Is there a port near here?
Can't you hear the foghorns?
Are you drunk?
No.
Thank you.
Mr. Sudo.
What are you doing here?
Grandma, call the police.
Call them. Now!
Mr. Sudoh...
Miss Sakakibara?
You are Miss Sakakibara?
You came to see him?
As you well know,
he's on a journey
of no return.
You came to hear me sing.
I'm so happy.
We were once rivals.
We're true friends now.
I'll sing then.
This bench is my stage.
I'm so happy to have
so many people here.
Hello!
Hello.
Louder, please.
All together now. Hello!
Hello.
With more spirit.
Hello!
Yes, hello.
They'll blame me, Missus.
Let's go back, please.
True friends, right?
Where's Mr. Sudoh?
Mr. Sudoh!
What happened?
Your name?
Where are you from?
She didn't enter the house.
- Look at this!
- Is this yours?
She tried to climb the stairs and fell.
Are you hurt?
Answer us properly.
Who are you?
- She smells of alcohol.
- She's weird.
Wait!
She is my friend.
Let her go.
She's that vocalist.
She's a bit...
So is her husband.